(Leonard:)Howard, just come in here.
(Penny:)Yeah, come on, Raj.
(Raj:)Wait, did Amy make
her spinach dip?
(Sheldon:)She did.
And I'm gonna eat it all!
(door slams)
(Howard:)So what the hell happened?
(Leonard:)Oh, I just ran out of patience
with Sheldon's nonsense.
(Howard:)Tell me about it.
I've had it with Raj, too.
(Amy:)You know, like women, men have
a monthly hormone cycle.
(Amy:)Dips in testosterone
can cause irritability.
(Howard:)Interesting.
(Howard:)Maybe my male cycle synced up
with Raj's actual period.
(Leonard:)If Sheldon's testosterone
dipped, he'd become a butterfly.
(knocking on door)
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Maybe someone's here
to apologize.
(Stuart:)Hey, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Stuart.
(Raj:)Uh...
(Stuart:)Is this not a dress-up party?
(Sheldon:)No.